(Raj:)And we made it in only three hours.
(Raj:)- Sounds just like store-bought.
- Heh, heh.
(Howard:)Okay, give me a superhero pose...
(Howard:)...and I will scan you into the computer
for your action figure.
(Raj:)Oh, I wish I was in better shape.
(Howard:)Stop holding your stomach in,
I'll give you a six-pack with the computer.
(Raj:)Oh, okay, great.
(Raj:)Now, I can look like Val Kilmer
as Batman...
(Raj:)...instead of Val Kilmer
as he looks today.
(Howard:)All right. You can suck it in a little bit.
Cooper, we have a problem.
Your work is really not
at the level I expected it to be.
I know. Go ahead and mock me.
But use small words so I understand.
Don't play dumb with me.
We both know what your problem is.
- We do?
- You have a girlfriend.